<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bidirectional Workflows: e-Referrals on OSCAR CDX Interoperability User Manual</title>
    <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bidirectional Workflows: e-Referrals on OSCAR CDX Interoperability User Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipient Registry</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_19/</guid>
      <description>The CDX infrastructure has a provider registry, which contains address information about all CDX-capable providers and clinics.
OSCAR has traditionally kept its own database of specialists. The CDX extension of OSCAR allows users to query the CDX provider registry and add/edit CDX capable providers in OSCAR&amp;rsquo;s database.
Adding new CDX-capable specialists The “Add Specialist” UI has been extended to add CDX-capable specialists (click the Add CDX-Enabled Specialist link at the top).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sending an e-Referral</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_20/</guid>
      <description>E-referrals are created in the usual way (like normal “consultations”) . Of course, it is important to select a CDX-capable specialist as the “Consultant”. These specialists are clearly marked in the dropdown box with a “(CDX)” prefix to their names (see below). They are also at the top of the list of specialists.
Some providers may work for more than one clinic. In this case, the user can select a specific clinic to direct the referral to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking the status of a Referral</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_21/</guid>
      <description>The user can validate whether an e-referral was sent and delivered by viewing the left side bar of the e-referral. Sent documents are shown with the time and date they were sent to the CDX messaging system.
  Checkmark shows that document was delivered to recipients   If a document has been sent to the CDX system but it has not been downloaded by the recipient clinic yet, OSCAR will show a cloud symbol instead of a check mark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating a Referral</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_22/</guid>
      <description>The user can send updates of e-referrals simply by re-opening the consultation form, updating some information and pressing on Update &amp;amp; Send CDX e-Referral.
  Referral form updated with additional information   The consultation form keeps track of all versions of a referral request that have been sent (and delivered).
  Initial referral and later update   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receiving Responses</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/015_sending/cdx_23/</guid>
      <description>Responses received from a specialist (via CDX) will arrive in the receiver&amp;rsquo;s inbox (as described in the receiving chapter)
However, they also show up on the consultation form under &amp;ldquo;Response Received&amp;rdquo; at the side bar.   Indication of a response received   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>