<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CDX Composer on OSCAR CDX Interoperability User Manual</title>
    <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CDX Composer on OSCAR CDX Interoperability User Manual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sending</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/cdx_24_sending/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/cdx_24_sending/</guid>
      <description>CDX Composer can be used to send different CDX documents like information request, progress note and patient summary from a single interface.
  CDX Composer UI   Patient Patients can be directly searched by their first and last name and added to the document.
Primary Recipient(s) and Secondary Recipient(s) The CDX infrastructure has a provider registry, which contains address information about all CDX-capable providers and clinics.
Even though, OSCAR has traditionally kept its own database of specialists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/cdx_25_history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/cdx_25_history/</guid>
      <description>History CDX Composer keeps track of all the Cdx documents sent through CDX Composer. &amp;gt; CDX Composer → History
  CDX Composer History   Users can view the detailed sent document by clicking on the &amp;ldquo;View&amp;rdquo; button on the history page.
  Sent document view    Documents sent through CDX Composer have also been logged and visible in the patient e-chart section as shown in the pic below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receiving and Reply</title>
      <link>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/cdx_26_reply/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 11:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simbioses.github.io/cdxuserman/006_for_users/021_cdxcomposer/cdx_26_reply/</guid>
      <description>Receiving Responses received from a specialist (via CDX) will arrive in the receiver&amp;rsquo;s inbox (as described in the receiving chapter)   Inbox   Reply CDX Composer allows user to respond back or reply to the incoming or received documents. &amp;gt; Inbox → Specific Message → Reply
Users can open any CDX document from the inbox to see a &amp;ldquo;Reply&amp;rdquo; button in the top right side as shown in the pic below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>